<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Snap Decision Test</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="hello">Hello World, ParseStarterProjectActivity!</string>
    <string name="Username">Username</string>
    <string name="Password">Password</string>
    <string name="LoginBtn">Login</string>
    <string name="SignupBtn">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="LogoutBtn">Log Out</string>
    <string name="ExitBtn">Exit</string>
    <string name="Welcome">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_new_user_message">NewUserMessageActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_welcome">WelcomeActivity</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="study_terms">PURPOSE AND BACKGROUND\n\n
                Dr. Pamela Reinagel at the University of California, San Diego is conducting a research
study to learn about how people make snap decisions based on ambiguous sensory cues.
You have been invited to participate because you are a healthy volunteer, 18 years old or
older, with normal or corrected vision and hearing. There will be approximately 100
volunteers in this study.\n\n
PROCEDURES\n\n
If you agree to be in this study, data from any tests you complete within this app,
including any you have already completed, will be anonymously uploaded to our data
server for research analysis. The uploaded data will be limited to: the time of each
attempt, ambient light level, stimulus shown, response made, and reaction time.
You do not have to do anything extra to participate in the study. You can continue to
perform self-tests at any time, for any duration, just as if you were not participating. Your
data will be automatically uploaded to our server when your device has wireless
connection to the internet. Your participation lasts until you choose to withdraw or the
study ends. There will be no cost to you for participating in this study. There is no compensation for
participating in this study.\n\n
RISKS AND INCONVENIENCES\n\n
Participation in this study may involve some added risks or discomforts. These include
the following:\n\n
1.\vThere is a potential for the loss of confidentiality. To minimize this risk, neither
your name nor any other identifying information will be recorded at any time. Your
data will be identified only by a unique random code generated on your device, that
cannot be traced back to you. Research records will be kept confidential to the extent
allowed by law. Research records may be reviewed by the UCSD Institutional Review Board.\n\n
2.\vBecause this is a research study, there may also be some unknown risks that are
currently unforeseeable. You will be told if there are any significant new findings
affecting your risk.\n\n
BENEFITS\n\n
There is no direct benefit to you of participating.  Society may benefit from advancing
our understanding of human cognition. In the future this basic knowledge could lead to
the development of useful cognitive or clinical tests or training methods.\n\n
QUESTIONS\n\n
The study has been explained to you, and you have had an opportunity to ask questions
by contacting the investigator at preinagel@ucsd.edu.  If you have other questions or
research-related problems, you may reach Dr. Pamela Reinagel at preinagel@ucsd.edu.
You may call the Human Research Protections Program Office at (858) 657-5100 to
inquire about your rights as a research subject or to report research-related problems.
Participation is entirely voluntary. You are under no obligation to take part in this study.
You may refuse to participate or withdraw at any time without jeopardy.\n\n
CONSENT\n\n
You will be able to view this document again at any time within the app. Clicking “Yes I
consent to participate” will server as your signature, indicating that you have read this
information and you agree to participate:</string>

</resources>
